thetradenews.com 2019-04-30

# Privacy Policy - The TRADE

_Last updated: 22 May 2018_

This privacy policy describes how The TRADE maintains, uses and shares information that it may collect when you use any of the following websites that it operates (the “Sites”):

  * THETRADENEWS.COM

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. Any such changes will be posted here.

 **Personal Information:**  Some of the information that we collect when you use this Site, such as your name, company name, postal address, email address, credit card number or telephone number, may allow you to be identified. We call this information “Personal Information.”

 **Registration:**  When you register on a Site, such as to receive a publication or email newsletter, you will be asked to provide certain Personal Information, which we use to provide the publication or newsletter to you.

 **Surveys:**  We may ask you to complete surveys or opinion polls from time to time. Participation is voluntary. We only use the information that we collect from surveys in an aggregate manner, not in individually identifiable form.

 **Blogs and Forums:  **Our Sites may provide an opportunity for you to post information to blogs, forums or other public areas. By doing so, you consent to the posting of any Personal Information that you provide. You should be aware that such Personal Information can be read, collected, or used by other visitors to these public areas. We have no control over how these visitors use your Personal Information.

 **Visitors:  **If you are just visiting the Sites and not registering for a publication, contacting us or posting to a public area of the Sites, we do not ordinarily collect any Personal Information about you except through web logs (see below), or if you choose to share information with us in any other way. In that case, we will obtain the information that you provided and will use it to respond to your inquiry or to fulfill your request if we can. We do not share any of this information with anyone else, except to respond to your request, if you consent, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

 **Web Logs** : We maintain web logs that automatically record basic information about everyone who visits the Sites. We use web log information to help us design our websites, to identify popular features, and for other managerial and analytic purposes. We may also use web logs to help identify any person attempting to break into, damage or misuse any of the Sites. These logs contain:

  * The Internet domain from which you access any of the Sites.
  * Your IP address.
  * The type of browser and operating system that you use.
  * The date and time you visited any of the Sites.
  * The pages that you visited on any of the Sites.
  * The address of the website you linked from to get to any of the Sites.

 **Cookies** : We use cookies, web beacons and similar technology to help you navigate the Sites, to allow us to learn how you use the Sites and to improve the Sites. Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not reveal any Personal Information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our Sites. However, once you choose to provide Personal Information to a Site, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. If you decide not to permit cookies on your computer, this may affect your ability to use the Sites.

 **Communicating with You.  **We may use information that we collect from you for the purpose of communicating with you and responding to your inquiries. Those communications could, for example, take the form of news updates, promotions for products or services that we or one of our marketing partners provide, or e-newsletters.

 **Service Providers:  **We sometimes contract with third party service providers to perform functions for us. These service providers may be given access to your information for the purpose of performing those functions, but they may not use this information for any other purpose.

 **Marketing Partnerships:  **From time to time, we may make your Personal Information available to other reputable organizations to market, or allow others to market, products or services that may be of interest to you.

 **Business Transfers:  **If we were to transfer all or substantially all of our assets, or the assets pertaining to one or more Site(s), to another company, one of the assets we would likely include in the transfer is the relevant database of Personal Information.

 **Webinars:  **From time to time, a Site may host webinars or similar events in conjunction with cosponsors. We may share Personal Information of attendees of these webinars with the cosponsors.

 **Disclosures for Legal Reasons:**  We will disclose Personal Information when we are required to do so by law, regulation or securities exchange requirement, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or when we believe such disclosure is appropriate to protect our legal rights or to safeguard anyoneâ€™s property or safety.

 **Overseas Transfers:  **We are a global business. In order to provide you with products or services, we may transfer your Personal Information to other parts of our organization or to our agents in countries outside of your own. By using this Site, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information in this manner. Although the data protection legislation in some countries may differ from that in your own country, we will make good faith efforts to ensure Personal Information is protected as described in this privacy policy.

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Sites. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this Site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, please [Click here](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/75843397 "Privacy Policy")  

We may offer you the opportunity to contact other companies, such as advertisers, marketing affiliates and content providers, to obtain information or to buy products or services. You decide when and whether to give your Personal Information to these companies. If you provide information, its use and security is governed by the policies and practices of those companies and not by this privacy policy.

We make no representations or warranties about any of these other companies or their privacy or security policies. Once you click through to an unaffiliated website, this privacy policy no longer applies. We strongly urge you to read the applicable policies of these other companies and their websites.

If you would like us to stop sending you email or other communications; would like us not to disclose your Personal Information to marketing partners or advertisers; or would like to access your registration information to correct or delete it, you may send us a request at[ info@www.thetradenews.com](mailto:optout@www.thetradenews.com).

5\. Security 

We maintain all Personal Information with physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards to help ensure the security and confidentiality of the data against reasonably foreseeable risks. Security is designed to prevent unauthorized use, access, disclosure, destruction, and changes of data. For example, we restrict access to our computing facilities to individuals identified by management as needing access to perform their jobs. We also review changes in technology and security measures and regularly train our personnel.

The Sites are intended for use by adults. We do not target, or knowingly collect any Personal Information from, children under the age of 13.
